Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،
how dare you,
كيف تجرؤ،
How dare you kill Her Highness?
كيف تجرؤ على قتل صاحبة السمو؟
If I say I didn't kill him.
إذا قلت أنني لم أقتله.
Believe it or not?
صدق او لا تصدق؟
You still want to argue.
ما زلت تريد أن تجادل.
Kill them!
اقتلهم!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Which way are you going, Master?
أي طريق أنت ذاهب يا معلمة؟
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
the awakening skill of the military adviser,
مهارة الصحوة للمستشار العسكري ،
Advisor,
مستشار ،
as far as you can see,
بقدر ما تراه ،
Which way should I go?
أي طريق يجب أن أذهب؟
This way.
من هنا.
Okay,
تمام،
Hey,
يا،
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Advisor,
مستشار ،
which way should we go?
في أي طريق نذهب؟
Let's go that way.
دعنا نذهب بهذه الطريقة.
Okay,
تمام،
Hey,
يا،
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You don't listen to me.
أنت لا تستمع إلي.
Come on.
تعال.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Go that way.
اذهب بهذه الطريقة.
Master
يتقن
is at a fork in the road again,
عند مفترق طرق مرة أخرى ،
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Advisor, in your opinion,
المستشار برأيك
which way should we go?
في أي طريق نذهب؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Stop messing around.
توقف عن العبث.
Are you running for your life?
هل تركض من أجل حياتك؟
Master, you're the one who's making a scene
سيدي ، أنت من تصنع مشهدًا
Okay, I used to offer brilliant ideas,
حسنًا ، كنت أقدم أفكارًا رائعة ،
You turned a deaf ear to it.
لقد أدرت أذنًا صماء لذلك.
This time,
هذا الوقت،
I won't talk about it.
لن أتحدث عن ذلك.
Advisor, I was wrong.
المستشار ، كنت مخطئا.
Is it OK?
هل الامور على ما يرام؟
This time, I'll go wherever you say.
هذه المرة ، سأذهب أينما قلت.
I'll definitely listen to you, okay?
سأستمع إليك بالتأكيد ، حسنًا؟
Really?
حقًا؟
since
منذ
Master lost his way and came back.
ضل السيد طريقه وعاد.
I'll point to a clear path,
سأشير إلى مسار واضح ،
although the path is steep,
على الرغم من أن المسار شديد الانحدار ،
But with twists and turns,
ولكن مع التقلبات والانعطافات ،
chasing troops is not easy to move forward,
مطاردة القوات ليس من السهل المضي قدما ،
Take the path.
خذ الطريق.
What?
ماذا؟
Advisor, I should
المستشار ، يجب علي
take the main road.
اسلك الطريق الرئيسي.
Master,
يتقن،
you're teasing me again,
أنت تضايقني مرة أخرى ،
This is a matter of life and death.
هذه مسألة حياة وموت.
If you don't leave,
إذا لم ترحل ،
I'll leave.
سأرحل.
Don't, Advisor.
لا تفعل أيها المستشار.
I'm just showing you,
أنا فقط أريكم ،
I was right.
كنت على حق.
Advisor.
مستشار.
Master,
يتقن،
the alliance turned out to be a conspiracy.
اتضح أن التحالف كان مؤامرة.
They still want to kill us.
ما زالوا يريدون قتلنا.
However,
لكن،
Han Xuanzhi has to
هان Xuanzhi يجب أن
pay for his life.
دفع ثمن حياته.
Master,
يتقن،
who do you think killed Han Xuan Zhi?
من تعتقد أنه قتل هان شوان تشي؟
I don't know either.
لا اعرف ايضا.
But one thing I know for sure,
لكن هناك شيء واحد أعرفه بالتأكيد ،
that person definitely doesn't want us
هذا الشخص بالتأكيد لا يريدنا
to form an alliance with Black Rock City.
لتشكيل تحالف مع بلاك روك سيتي.
Desperate young man.
شاب يائس.
I'm awake.
انا مستيقظ.
Seeing how miserable you are,
ترى كم أنت بائسة ،
I'll give you the prize you accumulated
سأمنحك الجائزة التي جمعتها
in the previous stage.
في المرحلة السابقة.
It's really a way out.
إنها حقًا طريقة للخروج.
Judging from the way you look, you've already experienced
انطلاقا من الطريقة التي تبدو بها ، لقد جربت بالفعل
the dangers of the new stage.
مخاطر المرحلة الجديدة.
At this stage,
في هذه المرحلة،
you will be faced with multiple tasks at the same time,
ستواجهك مهام متعددة في نفس الوقت ،
These tasks vary in difficulty.
هذه المهام تختلف في الصعوبة.
You can choose to do it or not.
يمكنك أن تختار أن تفعل ذلك أم لا.
But every choice you make
لكن كل خيار تقوم به
will affect and determine
ستؤثر وتحدد
you and your partner,
أنت وشريكك ،
The fate and ending of the future.
مصير ونهاية المستقبل.
It's getting harder and harder.
إنها تزداد صعوبة.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
it's all my fault that I was willful
كل خطأي كنت متعمدا
and caused everyone to fall into this cave.
وتسبب في سقوط الجميع في هذا الكهف.
adviser
مستشار
It's just a trivial matter. Why bother?
إنها مجرد مسألة تافهة.  لماذا تهتم؟
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
Advisor.
مستشار.
Don't blame yourself.
لا تلوم نفسك.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I won't be a burden to you.
لن أكون عبئا عليك.
She died and lived after her death.
ماتت وعاشت بعد وفاتها.
Everything is under control.
كل شيء تحت السيطرة.
With this magic weapon, we can break through.
مع هذا السلاح السحري ، يمكننا الاختراق.
It's gone.
لقد ذهب.
Why is it gone?
لماذا ذهب؟
I didn't expect this magic weapon to have durability.
لم أكن أتوقع أن يتمتع هذا السلاح السحري بالمتانة.
Why do you still have it?
لماذا لا يزال لديك؟
This is.
هذا هو.
There are side effects.
هناك آثار جانبية.
Master,
يتقن،
with the magic weapon, we are even more powerful now.
مع السلاح السحري ، نحن أقوى الآن.
Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،